brickhost.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Statement | Brickhost

BrickHost – Privacy Statement

We want to assure you that BrickHost is dedicated to protecting your privacy online. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us by email at [privacy@brickhost.com.](mailto:privacy@brickhost.com.)

BrickHost is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our Web sites as well as the privacy of our actual customers.

For visitors, we’ve structured our Web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

For prospective and existing customers and partners, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with BrickHost.  

Visitors to Our Web Site

What information do we collect?

When you visit our Web site, our Web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP’s domain, the time you accessed our Web site, and the pages from within our Web site that you visit and is not personally identifiable information except as needed to prevent fraud or abuse of the system.

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a Web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Most web browsers allow you to control this use of cookies. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you elect to disable cookies, please keep in mind that you will not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience on our Web site. It is possible that some portions of the site will not function properly or may perform more slowly if you choose to reject cookies.

Our Web site allows for a chat function. Chat functions allow you to participate in “live” online conversations with us on our Web site. Although the transcripts from the chats may be stored internally on in-house servers for our records only, we collect no personally identifiable information about you when you participate unless you choose to provide that information to us.

How do we use this information?

The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze Web traffic, improve the content of our Web site and improve your experience on our Web site.

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes the products and costs of items that visitors purchase and the pages visited. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can “opt-out” of this website analysis tool by sending an email to [optout@brickhost.com.](mailto:optout@brickhost.com.)

Our Web site provides links to other Web sites, sites that may be maintained by companies that are not affiliates of ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites and we encourage you to use caution. In particular, we recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each site to confirm the sites policies are acceptable to you. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

BrickHost Customers

What information do we collect?

When you sign up for BrickHost’s services, you provide us with both contact and payment information. Contact information typically includes your name, address, and phone number. Payment information typically includes your billing address and your credit card number.

While you are a BrickHost customer, we manage information with regard to your account status, choice of services, and customer logs. In addition, we may store customers’ electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications.

How do we use this information?

We use the contact information you provide us to establish our service for you. We use payment information for payment processing purposes only. We create and maintain other information such as customer account status, choice of services, and customer logs in the normal course of providing service.

BrickHost will never share customer information with partners/third parties. However, BrickHost may use customer information to provide customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products if you have chosen to receive such offers.
